charlestonsw.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy | Store Locator Plus™

## Who we are

Store Locator Plus, LLC is a Charleston, South Carolina company that exists 100% in the United States of America.

Our website address is: [https://www.storelocatorplus.com](https://www.storelocatorplus.com/).

This privacy policy pertains to the use of our web properties.

If you use our software on your websites via a plugin or embedded JavaScript snippet you should also read our [“Third Party Site’s Use of Store Locator Plus” Privacy Policy](https://www.storelocatorplus.com/third-party-sites-use-of-store-locator-plus-privacy-policy/) and combine it with the public Privacy Policy you have published on your site or within your mobile app.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

Because we are a web app company we collect typical web app information. Seriously, we now have to tell people about this?   The world has come to this?   Ok, here it goes…

IP addresses are collected by every freakin’ web server in existence including the one on this site.   It usually doesn’t have your personal name associated with it but it almost certainly has an IP address that could be tracked down to someplace near you.  Maybe even your home.    Unless you are using a proxy service, which if your are not just assume everyone knows EXACTLY where you are and what you are doing.   The NSA almost certainly does.   In fact they probably know you are reading this right now.    For the Love of God, you are using the Internet, just assume you have almost no privacy whatsoever.

That web server, by the way, also probably knows what TYPE of device you are using?   An iPhone, a Macbook, a probably crashing-at-this-very-moment Windows PC running an Edge browser that can barely show this Privacy Policy.   Yup, that is stored in about 3,297 servers, routers, cache services, and content delivery network nodes around the world.    Also not very likely to be associated with you personally but when combined with that IP address we just talked about some smart people, even those outside the NSA, probably have a good idea about some details on your life including what you just ate for breakfast.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Who we share your data with

In general we try not to share your personally identifiable data without anyone, even if they ask nicely.    It really is none of their business.  We only want to sell you some software to make putting maps and directories on your site easier.  We are not some shady-ass company that wants to make another $12 off selling some jerk-wad a list of our customers so they can spam the crap out of you or show you ads for hair spray.

However just by interacting with our sites there is a TON of data flying around which may, or may not, be used to identify you. Such as:

 _ **Payment Processors –**_ If you purchase a product or service from [Store Locator Plus](https://www.storelocatorplus.com/) , the information needed to process your payment is shared with Stripe.    Be sure to read [Stripe’s Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy/). If your purchased a product or service from Store Locator Plus prior to January 2018 the information needed to process your payment may have been shared with PayPal.    Be sure to read [PayPal’s Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

Email Services – If you have signed up for a mailing list, which will happen via an opt-in service if you purchased any of our paid WordPress plugins, your email and name and related purchase information is shared with MailChimp.  Go read the [MailChimp Privacy Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

 _ **Login Service Facilitators –**_ If you have an account created on our Demo site, the WordPress plugin store, or the MySLP SaaS service information you used to create your account, typically a user name and email address, is stored locally on our servers.    If you used a third-party service to facilitate your account login or creation the login information is shared with that service.   Some third-party login services include WordPress.org, Twitter, Facebook, and Google.   If you logged into any of our services with their login facilities you should read their Privacy Policy as well.   Since most of you reading this, all three of you since most of you fell asleep reading the first half-dozen regurgitated paragraphs above, are likely to at least have a WordPress.org login you should at least read the [WordPress.org Privacy Policy](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

 _ **Web Service Providers –**_ Most of our web presence is routed through several other service providers.     Amazon Web Service manages a lot of the infrastructure.   Go read the [AWS Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/) too.      We also run a lot of things through Sucuri proxy and web firewalls in an attempt to keep at least the basic “Script Kiddies” from crashing our sites.   Go read that [Sucuri Privacy Policy](https://sucuri.net/privacy) now.

 _ **Safety, Legal, and Law Enforcement Agencies –**_  We use and disclose Data as we believe necessary: (i) under applicable law; (ii) to enforce our terms and conditions; (iii) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, You or others; and (iv) to respond to requests from courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies, and other public and government authorities, which may include authorities outside your country of residence.

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site or any of our affiliated Store Locator Plus sites, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

We use and disclose Data as we believe necessary: (i) under applicable law, or payment method rules; (ii) to enforce our terms and conditions; (iii) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, You or others; and (iv) to respond to requests from courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies, and other public and government authorities, which may include authorities outside Your country of residence.

## Advertising

Those little ads at the bottom of some of our sites (which we’ve removed recently from most, if not ALL, of our sites) are great a tracking data.   They use hidden pixels and JavaScript trackers and follow you everywhere.  They may well know what site you were on three days ago before visiting us.   They know you visited that online pet store and ordered a gerbil.  They now know you love gerbils and are interested in map and directory software.  One of those ads we used to host was by SiteGround, so go read the Site Ground Privacy Policy.   There were also ads from the WordPress ad network, bu you already read the WordPress.org Privacy Policy from top-to-bottom, right?

## Security

We use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Data within our organization including the use of SSL-based websites with active security certificates. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If You have reason to believe that Your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if You feel that the security of Your account has been compromised), please [contact us](https://www.storelocatorplus.com/contact-us/) immediately.

## Use of products and services by minors

The Services are not directed to individuals under the age of eighteen (18), and we request that they not provide Personal Data through the Services.
